Privacy Notice - Binance
========================

Last updated: 02 December 2025

Binance (“Binance”, “we”, or “us”) is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers, service providers and website users and we take our data protection responsibilities with the utmost seriousness.

This Privacy Notice  describes how Binance collects and processes your personal data through the Binance websites and applications that are referenced in this Privacy Notice. It also informs you of how you can exercise your privacy rights, as applicable. 

Binance refers to an ecosystem comprising Binance websites (whose domain names include but are not limited to [www.binance.com/en](http://www.binance.com/en)), mobile applications, clients, applets and other applications that are developed to offer Binance products, and includes independently-operated platforms, websites and clients within the ecosystem (e.g., Binance’s Open Platform, Binance Launchpad, Binance Labs, Binance Charity, Binance DEX, Binance X, JEX, Binance Junior and fiat gateways). For the purposes of this Privacy Notice we have referred to this ecosystem as "**Binance Services**". 

You might find external links to third party websites on Binance websites. This Privacy Notice does not apply to your use of a third-party site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties, which are subject to their respective privacy policies.

If you have any questions regarding the processing of your personal data or if you believe your privacy rights have been violated, please contact our data protection officer [here](mailto:dpo@binance.com) and they will work to address any questions or issues that you have with respect to the collection and processing of your personal data.

1.  **Who does this Privacy Notice apply to?**

This Privacy Notice applies to all personal data processing activities carried out by us, across Binance Services. This Privacy Notice will apply to you:

1.  To the extent that you are a relevant stakeholder, customer or user of the Binance Services and based on where you reside, as further described below ("Customers").
    
2.  To the extent that you are not a relevant stakeholder, customer, or user of our services, but are using our website, this Privacy Notice also applies to you together with our Cookie Notice, which can be accessed [here](https://www.binance.com/en/cookie-privacy) ("Website Users").
    
3.  To the extent you participate in our events, as a participant or a presenter ("Event Attendees"). 

This Privacy Notice should therefore be read together with our Cookie Notice, which provides further details on our use of cookies on the website. Our Cookie Notice can be accessed [here](https://www.binance.com/en/cookie-privacy).

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Where You Reside | Services Provided | Operating Entity | Contact Address |
| France | Digital Asset Services Provider | Binance France SAS | 1 rue de Stockholm, 75008, Paris, France |
| Italy | Digital Asset Services Provider | Binance Italy S.R.L | Corso Europa n. 15, 20122, Milano (MI), Italy |
| Spain | Virtual Assets Services Provider | Binance Spain SL | C/ del Pinar, 5, 28006, Madrid |
| Sweden | Financial Institution | Binance Nordics AB | Mailbox 625, 114 11 Stockholm Sverige |
| Poland/Belgium | Digital Asset Services | Binance Poland Spółka z Ograniczoną Odpowiedzialnością | Ul. Aleje Ujazdowskie, No. 41, apt., locality Warsaw, 00-540, Poland |

This Privacy Notice does not apply to job applicants and candidates who apply for employment with us or to our employees whose personal data is subject to different privacy notices which are provided to such individuals in the context of their employment or working relationship with us. 

2.  **The Binance Entity Responsible for Looking After your Personal Data**

The Binance group is made up of different legal entities. In this regard, the controller of your personal data is the legal entity that determines the "means" and the "purposes" of any processing activities that it carries out. 

For global users, i.e. users that are not registered with a local regulated exchange, Nest Services Limited (a company incorporated under the laws of the Republic of Seychelles with registration number 238045 and address at House of Francis, Room 303, Ile Du Port, Mahe, Seychelles) is your operating entity and data controller, as of 31 August 2023.

For users within the European Economic Area and Switzerland that are registered with a [local regulated exchange](https://www.binance.com/en-GB/legal/licenses), your data controller is that entity, joint with Binance (Services) Holdings Limited (“BSHL”) (a company incorporated under the laws of Ireland with registration number 704568 and address at 6th Floor, South Bank House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4). 

For users outside the European Economic Area and Switzerland that are registered with a [local regulated exchange](https://www.binance.com/en-GB/legal/licenses), that exchange is your operating entity and your data controller.

For users within the European Economic Area and Switzerland (excluding the countries referenced in the table above), Nest Services Limited is your operating entity and Nest Services Limited is a joint controller with BSHL. BSHL has primary responsibility for your personal data. 

In the European Economic Area for data protection matters, VeraSafe has been appointed as Nest Services Limited's representative, pursuant to Article 27 of the General Data Protection Regulation of the European Union. If you are in the European Economic Area, VeraSafe can be contacted in addition to Binance’s Data Protection Officer, only on matters related to the processing of personal data. To make such an inquiry, please contact VeraSafe using this contact form: [https://verasafe.com/public-resources/contact-data-protection-representative](https://verasafe.com/public-resources/contact-data-protection-representative)  or via telephone at: +420 228 881 031. Alternatively, VeraSafe can be contacted at: VeraSafe Ireland Ltd, Unit 3D North Point House, North Point Business Park, New Mallow Road, Cork, T23AT2P, Ireland.

If you have any questions or concerns about how your data is processed, you may contact our Data Protection Officer (‘DPO’) as set out in Section 16 below. You may also contact your national data protection supervisory authority if you have any concerns or wish to make a complaint. Contact details for your national supervisory authority can be found [here](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/about-edpb/members_en). 

3.  **What Personal Data does Binance collect and process?**

Personal data is data that identifies an individual or relates to an identifiable individual. This includes information you provide to us, information which is collected about you automatically, and information we obtain from third parties.

Information you provide to us. To open an account and access our services, we'll ask you to provide us with some information about yourself or the person on whose behalf you are opening a sub-account (i.e. in the context of Binance Junior). This information is either required by law (e.g., to verify your identity and comply with “Know Your Customer” obligations), necessary to provide the requested services (e.g., you will need to provide your email address in order to open your account), or is relevant for certain specified purposes, described in greater detail below. In some cases, if we add services and features you may be asked to provide us with additional information.

In some cases, the provision of the personal data will be mandatory, and we inform you, where this is the case. Failure to provide the data required implies that Binance will not be able to provide you with the relevant services.

We may collect the following types of information from you:

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Category of Personal Data** | **Category of Data Subject** | **Types of Personal Data** |
| **Personal Identification Data.** | Customers | Full name, User ID, unique personal identifier, screen name, e-mail address, gender, home address, phone number, date of birth, nationality, proof of residency, proof of address, signature, utility bills, photographs, and a video or voice recording of you. |
| Service Providers | Full name, email address, phone number, User ID |
| Event attendees | Name, email, company, title, industry, address, phone number, meal preferences, social media domain, photograph, audio, video and CCTV recording. <br><br>  <br><br>Event evaluation data and recording of the voice and likeness of event presenters. |
| **User Account Information** | Customers and Service Providers | User ID, User Account Information |
| **Sensitive and Biometric Personal Data and Personal Data relating to criminal convictions and offences.** | Customers and Service Providers | Binance may also collect sensitive personal data when permitted by local law or with your consent, such as biometric information, for example to verify your identity by comparing the facial scan data extracted from your selfie or video with the photo in your government issued identity document.<br><br>Results of KYC and background checks. Where required by law, we may also process data relating to criminal convictions and offences as part of our verification checks. |
| **Government Identifiers** | Customers | Government issued identity documents such as passport, national identification number, national identity card details, drivers licence numbers. |
| **Institutional Information** _**(If you are an institutional customer)**_ | Customers | Proof of legal formation, personal identification data for all material beneficial owners, personal data about the board of directors senior persons responsible for the operations of the body corporate. |
| **Online Identifiers** | Website Users and Customers using our website, platform and other online services. | Username, avatars, profile picture, social media domains/ profiles (such as Telegram, X, Youtube etc.) and where relevant, social media metrics (e.g. audience metrics etc.). |
| **Financial Information** | Customers | Bank account information, payment card information, source of funding, source of wealth, Binance account information, Binance user ID, pay ID. |
| Service Providers and Event Attendees | Bank account number, routing number. |
| **Wallet Information** | Customers | Wallet address, wallet ID, and other information related to integrations that you select. |
| **Transaction Information** | Customers and Service Providers | Information about the transaction you make on our services, such as the name of the recipient, your name and e-mail. |
| **Information from Cookies** | Customers, Service Providers and Website Users | See our [Cookie Notice](https://www.binance.com/en/cookie-privacy) for more information. |
| **Employment Information** | Customers and Service Providers | Job title, salary wage rate, and company. |
| **Communications** | Customers, Service Providers and Website Users | Surveys responses, information contained in the Survey. Communications with us including screenshots, call recordings with our customer services team, communications (including chat history) with interfaces such as chatbots. |
| **Contact Information** | Customers and Service Providers | E-mail address, phone number, phone book contacts, country, region. |
| _**Where relevant**_**, Politically Exposed Person’s (“PEP”) Information** | Customers | Information on whether you (or someone close to you) holds a prominent public function or presence on sanctions lists. We may need to collect certain additional information to comply with our legal requirements or in our legitimate interest. The types of personal data collected will vary depending on the availability of PEP checks in your location and the identity services selected by us including but not limited with e.g. information extracted from a utility bill a user uploads or other information or documents provided by you, publicly available information from media searches, sanctions and PEP lists. |

Information we collect from you automatically. To the extent permitted under the applicable law, we may collect certain types of information automatically, for example whenever you interact with us or use the services. This information helps us address customer support issues, improve the performance of our sites and services, maintain and or improve your user experience, and protect your account from fraud by detecting unauthorized access.    

Information collected automatically from users of our online services such as our websites and applications - this includes our customers and service providers, to the extent they use our online services:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Category of Personal Data** | **Types of Personal Data** |
| **Browsing Information** | Device ID, browsing information such as name and version, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, internet connectivity data, network interaction history, operator and carrier data, login data, browser type and version, device type category and model, time zone setting and location data, language data, application version, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, other information stored on or available regarding the devices you allow us access to when you visit and use Binance Services. |
| **Usage Data** | Authentication data, security questions, click-stream data, public social networking posts, and other data collected via cookies or similar technologies.<br><br>Information about how our services are performing when you use them, e.g., error messages you receive, performance of the site information, other diagnosis data. |
| **Marketing and Research Information** | Identifiers – the IP address, or other online identifiers of a person, e-mail address if used for direct marketing, and name and address.<br><br>Demographic data - (e.g., income, family status, age bracket, gender, interests, etc).<br><br>Browser/web history data and preferences expressed through selection/viewing/purchase of services and content, information about your mobile device including (where available) type of device, device identification number, mobile operating system.<br><br>Analytics and profiles of the individuals based on the data collected on them. For more information about this please see our [Cookie](https://www.binance.com/en/cookie-privacy) Notice.<br><br>Interests or inferred interests and marketing preferences. |

Information we collect from our affiliates, third parties and public databases. From time to time, we may obtain information about you from our affiliates, third party and public databases sources such as KYC vendors, government / sanction websites, as required or permitted by applicable law.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Category of Personal Data** | **Type of Personal Data** |
| **Affiliates** | In accordance with applicable law, we may obtain information about you from the group of companies related to us by common control or ownership (“Affiliates”) as a normal part of conducting business, so that we may offer our Affiliates’ services to you.<br><br>We may obtain information about you such as Personal Identification Data, Transactional Information, Institutional Information, Usage Information. <br><br>For example, if you want to convert cryptocurrency into fiat and make withdrawals into your bank account, we might need to exchange information with Bifinity UAB. For more information about how Bifinity UAB processes this information you can check its Privacy Notice [here](https://www.binancecnt.com/en/about/policy/privacy-policy). |
| **Blockchain Data** | We may analyze public blockchain data, such as transaction ID’s, transaction amounts, wallet address, timestamps or transactions or events. |
| **Retail Merchant Information** | When conducting a transaction with a third-party merchant, the merchant may provide us with personal data about you such as name, contact information, transaction information. |
| **Public Database Information** | We obtain information about you from public databases, such as the United Nations Sanctions List, US ITA Consolidated Screening List, and the SEC EDGAR, including your name, address, email address, phone number, gender, national ID number and nationality/country of residence, date of birth, job role, public employment profile, listing on any sanctions lists maintained by public authorities, and other data as necessary. |

4.  **Why does Binance process personal data? Which legal bases are we relying on for our collection and processing of your personal data?**

Our primary purpose in collecting personal data is to provide the Binance Services in a secure, efficient, and smooth way. We generally use your personal data to deliver, provide, operate, the Binance Services, for content and advertising, and for loss prevention and anti-fraud purposes. For any such use, we will rely on an appropriate legal basis. Where processing involves sensitive personal data, we also rely on an additional legal justification to use such information. 

In summary, Binance relies on the following legal bases for its processing of your personal data:

1.  We process your personal data where necessary to enable us to take steps to offer you the services, process your acceptance of the offer and fulfil our obligations in the contract with you. 
    
2.  Processing of your personal data would also be necessary to enable us to meet our legal and regulatory obligations. For example, we are licensed and regulated by certain industry regulators and are required to provide some services in accordance with relevant regulatory rules, such tax rules, obligations to prevent and detect unlawful activities, among others. 
    
3.  The collection and use of some aspects of your personal data is necessary to enable us to pursue our legitimate commercial interests.  For instance, we have legitimate interests in operating our business and managing and developing our relationships with our customers and Service Providers, understanding and responding to inquiries, sharing data in connection with mergers and acquisitions and transfers of business, preventing and detecting fraud, and improving our services. 
    
4.  You may also provide us with your consent to receive certain services, marketing or communications. In such situations, you are not obliged to provide your consent, and you may choose to subsequently withdraw your consent at any stage once provided. 

Additional legal conditions for processing sensitive information and data relating to criminal records and offences. This may include: 

5.  Explicit Consent: We may rely on your explicit consent to collect and use sensitive personal data. Where we rely on your consent to collect and use your personal data, you are not obliged to provide your consent, and you may choose to subsequently withdraw your consent at any stage once provided. However, where you refuse to provide information that we reasonably require to provide the services, we may be unable to offer you the services and/or we may terminate the services if not possible to fulfil the services without the respective information. 
    
6.  Substantial public interests: if applicable law allows, we may collect and use personal data for a substantial public interest. We use your personal data, including biometric information for identity verification and information relating to criminal convictions or alleged offences to prevent and detect fraud, other financial crime, and crime generally.  
    
7.  We may also need to process some sensitive personal data for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims by us or third parties.

For further details on the specific purposes, types of information, legal bases (and conditions for sensitive personal data) as well as the categories of recipients, please refer to the table below:

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Why does Binance process my Personal Data?** | **Legal Basis for our use of personal data (EEA and Switzerland)** | **Data Recipient** |
| **Managing our contractual relationship with you.** <br><br>  <br><br>This includes creating and maintaining your account (and any sub-accounts)  when we use your personal data to take and handle orders and process payments.<br><br>  <br><br>The Category of Personal Data processed is Personal Identification Data, Institutional Information, Contact Information, Financial Information. <br><br>  <br><br>The consequences of not processing personal data   for such purposes is the inability to open an account (or sub-account) with us or the termination of an account where one is already open. | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract of which you are a party.<br><br>  <br><br>Processing is also necessary for the purpose of the legitimate interest pursued by us in managing our business. | Your personal data is shared with Binance Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and managing our contractual relationship with you.<br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers to assist with the hosting and operation of the business. |
| **To maintain and monitor legal and regulatory compliance.**<br><br>  <br><br>Most of our core services such as the exchange services are subject to strict and specific laws and regulations requiring us to collect, use and store certain personal data and process Personal Identification, Government Identifiers, Institutional Information, PEP Information, Contact Information, Financial Information and in some cases Sensitive Personal Data. For example, to comply with our Know Your Customer (“KYC”) obligations under applicable laws and regulations, and in particular to comply with Anti-Money Laundering laws and regulations or sanctions laws/regulations (e.g. funds transfer rules such as Travel Rules) or customer due diligence regulatory obligations. <br><br>  <br><br>If you do not provide personal data required by law, you may be unable to open an account, or we may have to close your account where it is already opened. | Processing is necessary to comply with our legal obligations under applicable laws and regulations, and Anti-Money Laundering laws and regulations.    <br><br>  <br><br>Processing is also necessary for the purpose of the legitimate interest pursued by us in taking preventive steps to ensure legal and regulatory compliance. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and maintaining compliance with legal obligations to which we are subject.<br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology vendors, KYC, AML vendors and compliance agencies to assist with ensuring our legal compliance. |
| **To verify your identity.** <br><br>  <br><br>We are generally required to collect various pieces of personal data to properly identify or verify your identity and comply with other specific anti-money laundering (“AML”) or sanctions laws/regulations (e.g. funds transfer rules such as Travel Rules). The types of personal data collected will vary depending on the checks and identity verification needs in your location and the identity services selected by us.  <br><br>Our verification processes also involve electronic identification through the comparison of your ‘selfie’ against your provided verification information (Biometric data processing). Also, as part of our KYC obligations, we may process your Personal Identification Information, Government Identifiers, Contact Information, PEP Information and Financial Information . Some of this information will be shared with third party identity verification service providers. <br><br>  <br><br>If you do not provide personal data required by law, you may be unable to open an account, or we may have to close your account where it is already opened. | Processing is necessary to comply with our legal obligations under applicable laws and regulations including AML or KYC related laws and regulations.    <br><br>Processing is also necessary for reasons of substantial public interest based on EU or EU Member State law. We are subject to EU  Anti-Money Laundering Directives and the relevant EU Member States' law implementing them.<br><br>Processing may be necessary for the purpose of the legitimate interest pursued by us in taking preventive steps to combat fraud and ensure accurate and efficient transactions. <br><br>In certain jurisdictions we may rely on your consent or explicit consent to process your personal data for the purposes of biometric identity verification. When you consent to Binance processing your personal data for such a specified purpose, you may withdraw your consent at any time, and we will stop processing your personal data for that purpose. The withdrawal of consent does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and maintaining compliance with legal obligations to which we are subject.<br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology vendors and KYC, AML vendors, compliance agencies and relevant counterparties to transactions to assist with ensuring our legal compliance and improving our AML checks and security. |
| **To ensure the accuracy of your personal data.**<br><br>  <br><br>We process your personal data when you provide us with your ID document. We use Optical Character Recognition ("OCR") technology, powered by AI, to extract important data in order to ensure accuracy of the information and improve business efficiency. The OCR engine overcomes the limitations of traditional OCR and is capable of highly accurate data extraction. <br><br>To verify any inconsistency in the ID documentation presented by you during account creation and KYC process.This process allows us to detect potential errors, missing information or mismatches between ID documents. <br><br>  <br><br>Binance also utilizes other AI powered technologies. These AI powered technologies only analyze the content submitted and do not access or process any other personal data beyond what is necessary for this purpose. Any results generated by the AI powered technologies are reviewed by a human to confirm accuracy and relevance. We take steps to protect your privacy as part of this process. <br><br>  <br><br>Binance values transparency and is committed to providing individuals with meaningful control over their interactions with AI powered technologies. If you are affected by the outputs or decisions generated by our AI powered technologies, you can request a review or an appeal of these results by contacting us [here](mailto:dpo@binance.com).<br><br>  <br><br>Additionally, we emphasize that any personal data you provide is solely used to facilitate and improve your experience with our services. We do not utilize this data to further train or develop any Al algorithms.<br><br>If you have any questions about how this AI-powered technology review works, please contact us [here.](mailto:dpo@binance.com) | Processing is necessary to comply with our legal obligations under applicable laws and regulations. <br><br>  <br><br>Processing is also necessary for the purpose of the legitimate interest pursued by us to improve our services and enhance our user experience. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and verifying the accuracy of your personal data.<br><br>  <br><br>We also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology vendors to assist with ensuring the accuracy of your personal data. |
| **Communicate with you on service and transaction- related matters.**<br><br>  <br><br>We use your personal data to communicate with you in relation to Binance services on administrative or account-related information. We will communicate with you to keep you updated about the Binance Services  for example, to inform you of relevant security issues, updates, or provide other transaction-related information. Without such communications, you may not be aware of important developments relating to your account that may affect how you can use our services. You may not opt-out of receiving critical service communications, such as emails or mobile notifications sent for legal or security purposes. | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract of which you are a party.<br><br>  <br><br>Processing is also necessary for the purpose of the legitimate interest pursued by us in providing you with service-related communication as this is essential to the proper functioning of our services. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and ensuring that we can communicate with you effectively. <br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology vendors to assist our effective communication with you. |
| **To provide customer services.** <br><br>  <br><br>We process your personal data when you contact us in order to provide support with respect to questions, disputes, complaints, troubleshoot problems, etc. | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract of which you are a party.    <br><br>  <br><br>Processing is also necessary for the legitimate interest pursued by us to communicate and respond to you effectively and to improve our services and enhance our user experience. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and ensuring that we can communicate with you effectively. <br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology and marketing vendors to assist our effective communication with you. |
| **To promote the safety, security, and integrity of our platform and Binance Services.**<br><br>  <br><br>We process your Identification Information, Institutional Information, Transactional Information, Contact Information, Financial Information, Browsing Information, Usage Data in order to enhance security, monitor and verify identity or service access, combat malware or security risks. We also process your personal data to verify accounts and related activity, find and address violations of our Terms and Conditions, investigate suspicious activity, detect, prevent and combat unlawful behaviour, detect fraud, and maintain the integrity of our platform and services. | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract of which you are a party and to comply with applicable security laws and regulations. <br><br>  <br><br>Processing is also necessary for the purpose of the legitimate interest pursued by us in preventing criminal activity. Without processing your personal data, we may not be able to ensure the security of our Services.<br><br>  <br><br>We use your personal data to provide functionality, analyse performance, fix errors, and improve the usability and effectiveness of Binance Services | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and ensuring that we can maintain the security and integrity of our platform.  <br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology vendors to assist with promoting the safety, security and integrity of our business. |
| **To provide and manage Binance Services.**<br><br>  <br><br>We process your personal data to provide the services to you, process your orders, facilitate transactions and to complete the transactions our Customers require. For example, when you want to use one of the transactional services (e.g. the exchange service) on our platform, we ask for certain information such as your identification, contact information, and payment information. | Processing is necessary for the performance of a contract of which you are a party.   <br><br>Processing is also necessary for the purpose of our legitimate interest in providing professional services, operating our business, and managing and developing our relationships with clients, suppliers and with you. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and ensuring that we can provide and manage our services effectively.   <br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology vendors and relevant counterparties to transactions to assist with providing and managing our services and platform. |
| **Use of social media and advertising platforms.** <br><br>  <br><br>We use the services of social media platforms or advertising platforms for purposes including marketing. This involves the processing of Usage Data and Browing Information. | We rely on your consent to process your personal data to use the services of advertising platforms. When you consent to processing your personal data for a specified purpose, you may withdraw your consent at any time, and we will stop processing your personal data for that purpose. The withdrawal of consent does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.<br><br>  <br><br>Processing is also necessary for the purpose of the legitimate interest pursued by us in communicating about our services or products. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and ensuring that we can communicate with you effectively. <br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology and marketing vendors to assist our effective communication with you. |
| **To provide you with promotions and/or donations.**<br><br>  <br><br>We use your information to provide you with promotions, including offers, rewards, and other incentives for using Binance Services. This would also include to enable you to partake in a prize draw, competition or complete a survey.<br><br>  <br><br>We may also use your information to determine your eligibility for donations. | For website users and/or donations, processing is necessary for the purpose of our legitimate interest in promoting our business by engaging with consumers through competitions or prize draws, to reward your customer loyalty, or to aid you in times of emergency.    <br><br>For customers we rely on your consent to process your personal data to provide you with promotions. When you consent to processing your personal data for a specified purpose, you may withdraw your consent at any time, and we will stop processing your personal data for that purpose. The withdrawal of consent does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business.<br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology and marketing vendors to assist with offering such promotions and/or donations. |
| **To do research, auditing, reporting, budgeting and other business operations purposes and to innovate and improve our services.**<br><br>  <br><br>We carry out surveys to learn more about your experience using Binance Services. We also use your information to support research and development and drive innovations of our services and products. This information will also be used for marketing purposes. | Processing is necessary for the purpose of the legitimate interest pursued by us to improve our business and platform and ultimately provide a better service to you. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and ensuring that we can continue to innovate and improve our services.  <br><br>  <br><br>We also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology and marketing vendors to assist with such business operations purposes. |
| **For internal business purposes and record keeping.** | Processing is necessary to comply with our legal obligations to keep certain records for internal business and research purposes. <br><br>  <br><br>Processing is also necessary for the purpose of the legitimate interest pursued by us to keep records to ensure your compliance with the contractual obligations pursuant to the agreement (“Terms and Conditions”) governing our relationship with you. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and ensuring that we maintain certain records. <br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology vendors to assist with effective record keeping. |
| **Recommendations and personalisation.**<br><br>  <br><br>We use your information to recommend features and services that might be of interest to you, identify your preferences, and personalise your experience with Binance services. | We rely on your consent to process your personal data for personalised advertising and the deployment of cookies. <br><br>  <br><br>Processing is also necessary for the purpose of our legitimate interest to provide a personalised service to our customers, based upon our understanding of your preferences. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and ensuring that we maintain certain records. <br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology vendors to assist with effective record keeping and recommendations. |
| **To provide marketing communications to you.**<br><br>  <br><br>We use your information based on your consent to send you targeted marketing communications through email, mobile, in-app, Telegram, and push notifications. We also use your information to carry out profiling for marketing purposes. Transactional account messages and communications regarding our business relationship will not be affected even if you opt-out from marketing communications. | Where required by applicable law, we rely on your consent to process your personal data for marketing purposes. When you consent to processing your personal data for a specified purpose, you may withdraw your consent at any time and we will stop processing your personal data for that purpose. The withdrawal of consent does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. <br><br>  <br><br>Where we carry out profiling for marketing purposes, for example to establish what Binance Services or promotions you may be interested in, this processing is based on our legitimate interest in ensuring the high-quality delivery of our products and services and also continuously improving our products and services. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and ensuring that we can communicate with you effectively.  <br><br>  <br><br>We also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology and marketing vendors to assist with ensuring effective communication. |
| **In relation to events we host and/ or organise.**<br><br>  <br><br>As an Event Attendee, we collect your Personal Identification Data and Financial Information to register you for our events, create your account, if relevant, provide you with updates relating to the event. We may also process financial information to facilitate the ticketing process at the event. <br><br>  <br>  <br><br>If you are a presenter at one of our events, in addition to the information above, we may process your voice recording and event evaluations.<br><br>  <br><br>Where you consent to the disclosure of your personal data to other sponsors, exhibitors and third parties, we may share your information with such third parties to provide you with the information you have consented to receiving.  <br><br>  <br><br>We also need to process some personal data to ensure the safety of our events and to plan future events. | Processing is necessary for the purpose of our legitimate interest to produce, organise and host events. We also have a legitimate interest in promoting and evaluating the event.<br><br>  <br><br>To the extent that your participation / engagement with the event creates a contractual relationship with us, the processing is also necessary for the performance of a contract of which you are a party.<br><br>  <br><br>We rely on your consent to process and share your personal data for marketing purposes. When you consent to processing your personal data for a specified purpose, you may withdraw your consent at any time. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of conducting our business and assisting with organising events and related processes.   <br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology and marketing vendors to assist with organising such events and related processes. |
| We use cookies and similar technologies as part of our Service. <br><br>  <br><br>Our Cookie Notice can be accessed [here](https://www.binance.com/en/cookie-privacy).<br><br>. | Where required by applicable law, we rely on your consent to place cookies and similar technologies on your device. When you consent to processing your personal data for a specified purpose, you may withdraw your consent at any time and we will stop processing your personal data for that purpose. The withdrawal of consent does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of operating our business.<br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology vendors to assist with the operation, security and analysis of the Binance Services. |
| **To comply with law, legal obligations, regulations, law enforcement, government, and other legal requests, court orders, ongoing or reasonably anticipated litigation or investigation, or disclosure to tax authorities.** <br><br>  <br><br>This includes data protection audits and impact assessments, assisting with our legal departments' case handling and coordination and facilitating your legal representation in court or during settlement negotiations. | Processing is necessary to comply with our legal obligations under applicable laws and regulations. <br><br>  <br><br>We may also rely on legitimate interests in taking preventive steps to ensure legal and regulatory compliance and responding to legal requests where we are not compelled to by applicable law but have a good faith belief that it is required by law in the relevant jurisdiction.<br><br>  <br><br>Additionally, we may rely on our legitimate interests in properly assessing and investigating claims and complaints and maintaining accurate records of claims and complaints received. | Your data is shared with Affiliates as a part of operating our business and ensuring compliance with the obligations to which we are subject. <br><br>  <br><br>We may also share your information with Service Providers, including, third party technology vendors, legal advisers and claims investigators to assist with ensuring compliance with the relevant requirements. |

5.  **Automated Decisions, Profiling and our use of Artificial Intelligence**

We also conduct automated decision-making, including profiling. An automated decision can be made based on an assessment carried out automatically using technology. In some cases, these may involve evaluating behaviour or making predictions about you, which are relevant to the service you require ("Profiling"). You have a right to object to decisions involving the use of your personal data, which have been taken solely by automated means. See Section 12 below, "Right to contest to a decision based solely on automated processing".

Additionally, we use artificial intelligence ("AI") technology to extract important data in order to ensure the accuracy of information, check for inconsistencies, detect potential errors, missing information and data mismatches.  The processing activities carried out using AI technology should not have any significant impact on you.  

6.  **Can Children Use Binance Services?**

Binance provides Binance Junior to minors, which is a way for those aged between 6 and the age of majority in their jurisdiction (which is 18 in most jurisdictions but can be up to 21) to learn about cryptocurrencies and safely use the platform with the help of their parents or legal guardians, by enabling a parent or legal guardian to set up a sub-account of their own Binance account for their minor. Binance Junior aims to provide a safe and educational environment for those aged 6 and above to learn about crypto and blockchain technology. See the [Binance Junior Privacy Notice](https://www.binance.com/en/about-legal/privacynotice-binance-junior) for more information about how Binance processes personal data in the context of Binance Junior, but this Privacy Notice should always be referred to for full details of our processing of Personal Data across our services.

Other than Binance Junior, Binance does not allow anyone under the age of 18 to use Binance Services and nor do we knowingly request or collect any information about persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not provide any personal data to Binance Services  (other than in the context of Binance Junior).

If a User or Customer submitting personal data (other than for Binance Junior) is suspected of being younger than 18 years of age, Binance will require the relevant Customer or User to close their account and will take steps to delete the individual’s information as soon as possible.    

In compliance with applicable privacy laws and regulatory requirements, we will retain Date of Birth (DOB) information when an individual who is under the legal age attempts to complete the Know Your Customer (KYC) identity verification process. This retention is necessary to prevent repeated attempts to re-register while an individual is under the legal age and to protect the integrity and security of our services by prohibiting underage access to our platform.

7.  **What About Cookies and Other Identifiers?**

We use cookies and similar tools to enhance your user experience, provide our services, enhance our marketing efforts and understand how customers use our services so we can make improvements. Depending on applicable laws in the region you are located in, the cookie banner on your browser will tell you how to accept or refuse cookies. A copy of our Cookie Notice is available [here](https://www.binance.com/en/cookie-privacy).    

8.  **How and Why, We Share Your Personal Data?**

We may share your personal data with third parties (including other Binance entities) if we believe that sharing your personal data is in accordance with, or required by, any contractual relationship with you (including Binance Terms & Conditions) or us, applicable law, regulation or legal process. When sharing your personal data with other Binance entities, we will use our best endeavours to ensure that such entities are either subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice. For example, depending on where you reside and the entity responsible for running KYC checks. For more information, please refer to Section 2 "The Binance entity Responsible for looking after your Personal Data".

We may also share personal data with the following persons or in the following circumstances:

*   Binance Affiliates: Personal data that we process and collect may be transferred between Binance companies as a normal part of conducting business and offering our services to you. See Section 2 "The Binance entity responsible for looking after your Personal Data" and Section 3 “What Personal Data does Binance collect and process?”. Transfers within Binance group are subject to contractual commitments that provide for an adequate level of protection for your personal data. 
    
*   Third parties: we may disclose your personal data in order to perform functions related to the service or based on your instructions. 

1.  We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include analysing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments, transmitting content, and assessing and managing credit risk, CTF/AML service providers (for the purposes of transaction monitoring), security service providers (for investigating fraud and security incidents). The third-party service providers only have access to personal data needed to perform their functions but may not use it for other purposes. Further, they must process the personal data in accordance with our contractual agreements and only as permitted by applicable data protection laws. 
    
2.  In accordance with and as far as provided by applicable law, your personal data may also be shared by third parties (i.e. _another data controller_) upon exercising your right to data portability. Please refer to Section 12 "What Rights Do I Have?", for more information on data portability. 
    
3.  When you use third-party services (like when you connect your Binance account with your bank account) or websites that are linked through the Binance Services, the providers of those services or products may receive information about you that Binance, you, or others share with them. Please note that when you use third-party services or Binance affiliate services which are not governed by this Privacy Notice, their own terms and privacy policies will govern your use of those services and products.

*   _Third Party Independent Controllers_: Within the context of the services rendered by Binance, some of the third-party service providers and/or counterparties to the transactions may process your personal data as independent data controllers for their own purposes which may include but are not limited to:

1.  compliance with legal or regulatory obligations under applicable laws;
    
2.  prevention of criminal activity, fraud (including impersonation fraud), money laundering or other illicit activities by checking data against records of confirmed or suspected illegal activities; in connection with this purpose, the service provider may carry out profiling, statistical analysis and analytics in AML/CFT tendency using machine learning; 
    
3.  enhancing the effectiveness and quality of its fraud prevention services;
    
4.  user onboarding as the third party’s own client or customer;
    
5.  to use the services of financial institutions for fiat related transactions - user identification necessary to respond to data subject requests; and
    
6.  establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims (if applicable).

These third-party independent controllers rely on legal bases for data processing as disclosed in their respective privacy notices, accessible from their websites. Your personal data will be processed and retained according to the service providers’ retention schedules. You can request for more information about the identity of the third party service providers and their processing activities by [contacting Binance](mailto:dpo@binance.com). 

*   Legal Authorities or Legal requirements: We may share your information with courts, law enforcement authorities, regulators, attorneys or other third parties: (a) to comply with laws and legal obligations; (b) for the establishment, exercise, or defence of a legal or equitable claim; (c) to respond to law enforcement and regulatory requests, including (1) when we are legally required or compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order, search or seizure warrant, or similar legal procedure, or (2) for international law enforcement requests, pursuant to a mutual legal assistance treaty (MLAT) or letters of request; (d) to comply with one or more forms of “travel rules” that require our transmitting of your information to another financial institution, regulatory authorities or other industry partners; (e) when we determine in good faith that the disclosure of personal data is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of our customers, Binance, or others, including but not limited to preventing imminent physical harm or material financial loss; (f) to investigate violations of our Terms of Use or other applicable policies; or (g) to detect, investigate, prevent or address fraud or credit risk, other illegal activity or security and technical issues, to report suspected illegal activity or to assist law enforcement in the investigation of suspected illegal or wrongful activity. All such disclosures are subject to applicable data protection laws and our internal governance and legal review processes to ensure compliance with relevant privacy frameworks.

*   US Plea Agreements and US Monitors:  In accordance with our legal obligations and the terms of the US Plea Agreements\*, Binance may share personal data with the US Monitors\*\* and their agents acting as independent Data Controllers of the data they receive. The personal data shared may include, but is not limited to, account information, transaction details, and all other relevant data that is collected and processed by Binance, and may be  required by the US Monitors and their agents. Once the retention period expires, we will securely delete or anonymize the personal data that we hold, unless we are required to retain the data for longer in order to comply with applicable legal and regulatory requirements. The US Monitors will apply their own retention periods to the data they process as Data Controllers. We are committed to protecting your privacy and  are committed to sharing only relevant information to fulfill our legal obligations.

\*“US Plea Agreements” means the judgments and/or final orders entered in United States v. Binance Holdings Limited, No. 23-178RAJ (W.D. Wash) and In Re Binance Holdings Limited, et al, FinCEN No. 2023-04 (Financial Crimes Enforcement Network) (Consent Order). 

\*\*“US Monitors” means the compliance monitors appointed and/or retained, and any of their agents, pursuant to the terms of the US Plea Agreements entered in United States v. Binance Holdings Limited, No. 23-178RAJ (W.D. Wash) and In Re Binance Holdings Limited, et al, FinCEN No. 2023-04 (Financial Crimes Enforcement Network) (Consent Order). 

*   Business transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy other businesses or services. In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the user consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Binance or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, user information will be one of the transferred assets.
    
*   With your Consent: We also may disclose your personal data as may be described in a notice to you at the time the information is collected or before it is shared, or in any other manner to which you consent.

For further details on the specific purposes, types of information, legal bases (and conditions for sensitive personal data) as well as the categories of recipients, please refer to Section 4.

9.  **International transfers of Personal Data**

To facilitate our global operations, Binance may transfer your personal data to countries outside of your country of residence, including but not limited to jurisdictions outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and Switzerland. The EEA includes the European Union countries as well as Iceland, Liechtenstein, and Norway. Transfers outside of the EEA and/or your country of residence are sometimes referred to as “third country transfers”. These transfers may be made to countries that relevant authorities, such as the European Commission, have recognised as providing adequate data privacy safeguards and to some countries that are not subject to an adequacy decision (which includes participants under the EU Data Privacy Framework). 

We may transfer your personal data to our Affiliates, third-party partners, and service providers based throughout the world. In cases where we intend to transfer personal data to third countries or international organisations outside of your country of residence that are not subject to an adequacy decision and further safeguards are required, Binance puts in place suitable technical, organizational and contractual safeguards (including Standard Contractual Clauses), to ensure that such transfer is carried out in compliance with applicable data protection rules.

Personal data of Mandarin or Chinese speaking users may be accessed by Customer Support located in China, where the relevant users seek local language support. Any remote access from China to user data is carried out in accordance with necessary safeguards which ensure an adequate level of protection for personal data.

You have a right to obtain more information about the safeguards we have put in place to ensure the adequate protection of your personal data when this is transferred as mentioned above. To exercise this right, please contact us [here](mailto:dpo@binance.com). 

10.  **How We Secure Personal Data?**

We design our systems with your security and privacy in mind. We have appropriate security measures in place to prevent your information being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. We work to protect the security of your personal data during transmission and while stored by using encryption protocols and softwares. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of your personal data. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know.

If you detect or suspect that your device has been compromised by malware or suspicious software, we may request additional information to help secure your account and to protect the Binance platform. This may include screenshots you voluntarily share to assist us in identifying unauthorised access or suspicious activity, and malware-related data, such as the cryptographic hash of identified malware and links to suspicious files, to help investigate threats. Any data shared for these purposes will be used for security investigation and fraud prevention in accordance with our legal obligations and legitimate interest in maintaining platform integrity. We will handle this information security and limit access to authorised security and IT teams only.

Our security procedures mean that we may ask you to verify your identity to protect you against unauthorised access to your account. We recommend using a unique password for your Binance account that is not utilized for other online accounts and to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

11.  **What About Direct Marketing and Advertising?**

In order for us to provide you with the best user experience, we may share your personal data with our marketing partners for the purposes of targeting, modelling, and/or analytics as well as marketing and advertising.  Some of this analytics is conducted by the use of cookies and similar technologies. Please see our [Cookie Notice](https://www.binance.com/en/cookie-privacy) to understand the cookies we deploy on the Binance Services. 

We may also share your contact data with carefully selected third parties for marketing purposes to provide you with tailored information about products, services, promotions, and events that may be of interest to you. We will only share your contact data with third parties for marketing purposes if you have given your explicit consent to receive marketing updates.

We will give you the opportunity to refuse direct marketing and to set your advertising preferences when you register with our services and when we send you direct marketing via email. You have a right to object at any time to processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (see Section 15 below – "Right to object to direct marketing").

12.  **What Rights Do I Have?**

Subject to applicable law, as outlined below, you have a number of rights in relation to your privacy and the protection of your personal data. You have the right to request access to, correct, and delete your personal data, and to ask for aspects of your personal data to be provided to you or a third party of your choice in electronic format, to enable its reuse (data portability). You may also object to our processing of your personal data or ask that we restrict the processing of your personal data in certain instances. In addition, when you consent to our processing of your personal data for a specified purpose, you may withdraw your consent at any time. If you want to exercise any of your rights, please contact us [here](mailto:dpo@binance.com). These rights may be limited in some situations - for example, where we can demonstrate we have a legal requirement to process your personal data.

*   Right to access: you have the right to obtain confirmation that your personal data are processed and to obtain a copy of it as well as certain information related to its processing. Please follow the [FAQ](https://www.binance.com/en-GB/support/faq/how-to-use-binance-account-statements-e12bc83ec9ba4e96a076d2b4a4419182) for further information on how to access your account statement yourself. You can also check your device and IP address login’s via the dedicated “Account Activity Records” page located [here](https://www.binance.com/en-GB/my/security/account-activity). Please note that you have to login to your account first to obtain access;
    
*   Right to rectification: you can request the rectification of your personal data which are inaccurate and also add to it. You can also change your personal data in your account at any time;
    
*   Right to deletion: you can, in some cases, have your personal data deleted. Please follow the [FAQ](https://www.binance.com/en-GB/support/faq/how-to-delete-my-binance-account-f02c2640a1cd44e58de68e4a49d599f6) for further self-help information on how you can request that your account is deleted yourself. Please note that personal data may still be retained in the event of account deletion to comply with our legal obligations;
    
*   Right to object: you can object to our processing of your personal data. For instance, you have the right to object where you feel there are no longer sufficient legitimate grounds for us to continue processing your data or where we rely on legitimate interests to process your data;
    
*   Right to object to direct marketing:  you can object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes;
    
*   Right to restrict processing: you have the right, in certain cases, to temporarily restrict the processing of your personal data by us, provided there are valid grounds for doing so. We may continue to process your personal data if it is necessary for the defense of legal claims, or for any other exceptions permitted by applicable law;    
    
*   Right to contest to a decision based solely on automated processing: we use automated tools to make sure that you are eligible to be our customer taking into account our interests and legal obligations; if these automated tools indicate that you do not meet our acceptance criteria, we will not onboard you as our customer. Nevertheless, you have the right to require that decisions be reconsidered if they are made solely by automated means, without human involvement. You can exercise this right by contacting us [here](mailto:dpo@binance.com);
    
*   Right to portability: in some cases, you can ask to receive your personal data which you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, or, when this is possible, that we communicate your personal data on your behalf directly to another controller;
    
*   Right to withdraw your consent: for processing requiring your consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Exercising this right does not affect the lawfulness of the processing based on the consent given before the withdrawal of the latter; and
    
*   Right to lodge a complaint with the relevant data protection authority: We hope that we can satisfy any queries you may have about the way in which we process your personal data. However, if you have unresolved concerns, you also have the right to complain to the data protection authority in the location in which you live, work or believe a data protection breach has occurred. 

It is important to note that some of the rights above can only be exercised in certain circumstances. If we are unable to fulfil a request in relation to your rights, we will write to you to explain the reasons for refusal. If you require further information on your privacy rights, have any questions or objection as to how we collect and process your personal data, please contact us [here](mailto:dpo@binance.com). 

13.  **How Long Does Binance Keep My Personal Data?**

We keep your personal data to enable your continued use of Binance Services, for as long as it is required in order to fulfil the relevant purposes described in this Privacy Notice, and as may be required by law such as for tax and accounting purposes, compliance with Anti-Money Laundering laws, or to resolve disputes and/or legal claims or as otherwise communicated to you.

While retention requirements vary by jurisdiction, information about our typical retention periods for different aspects of your personal data are described below.

*   Personal Identifiable Data, Government Identifiers, Institutional Information, Financial and Transaction Information collected to comply with our legal obligations under financial or anti-money laundering laws may be retained after account closure for as long as is required under such laws.
    
*   Contact Information such as your name, email address and telephone number for marketing purposes is retained on an ongoing basis and until you (a) unsubscribe, or we (b) delete your account. Thereafter we will add your details to an unsubscribed list to ensure we do not inadvertently market to you.
    
*   Content that you post on our website such as support desk comments, photographs, videos, blog posts, and other content may be kept after you close your account for audit and crime prevention purposes.
    
*   Recording of voice calls with you may be kept for a period of up to six years, for audit/ compliance purposes and to resolve disputes and/or legal claims.
    
*   Information collected via cookies, web page counters and other analytics tools is kept for a period of up to one year from the date of the collection of the cookie of the relevant cookie or in line with applicable guidance from data protection authorities.

Where personal data is no longer needed for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Notice, we may de-identify the information in order to use it for statistical purposes or perform business analytics or service development. Anonymised data may be retained indefinitely.

14.  **Notices and Revisions**

Binance reserves the right to reasonably amend this Privacy Notice from time to time. You should check our websites and Binance Services (e.g. the privacy notice section in our app settings) frequently to see recent changes. We will update the “Last Updated” date accordingly at the beginning of this Privacy Notice. We will announce any material changes to this Privacy Notice on our website / platform or by sending an email that you have provided under your account. Your continued use of Binance after the changes to this Privacy Notice means that you understand such changes. 

Unless stated otherwise, our most recent Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

15.  **Languages**

This Privacy Notice may be published in different languages. In case of any discrepancy, this English version shall prevail. 

16.  **Contact Information**

If you have any concerns about privacy at Binance, please contact us, and we will try to resolve it. You also have the right to contact your local Data Protection Authority.

Our Data Protection Officer can be contacted [here](mailto:dpo@binance.com) and will work to address any questions or issues that you have with respect to the collection and processing of your personal data.

If you have a question about your account management, or Binance products or services the Data Protection Officer will not be able to assist you. In that case, please contact our Customer Support team using the following [link](http://www.binance.com/en/chat).

Please read the [FAQ](https://www.binance.com/en-GB/support/faq/how-to-delete-my-binance-account-f02c2640a1cd44e58de68e4a49d599f6) for further information on how you can delete your account.
